likethislist.com 2010-12-30

# Privacy Policy

**Question:**  
When I clicked on a page my friend liked it sent me here! Why?

**Answer:**  
hugefanpages.com uses Facebook’s “Social Plugins”. These plugins allow our visitors to “like” our pages. When someone “likes” our page, Facebook automatically shares the page on the user’s wall. One of your friends must have “liked” one of our pages that sent you here.  
We respect our visitors and do NOT link to any ADWARE, VIRUSES or MALWARE!

Privacy Policy for **_www.hugefanpages.com_**

At hugefanpages.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by hugefanpages.com and how it is used. 

**We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here<http://www.networkadvertising.me/managing/opt_out.asp>**

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.hugefanpages.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
hugefanpages.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

hugefanpages.comdisplays Google Ads please read the Adsense [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) for more information. 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at **likethislist@gmail.com**
